{"id": "61b3a5c8c9a882dcfcd2", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20070218.0019.LDC2009T13", "relation": "org:founded_by", "token": ["Tom", "Thabane", "resigned", "in", "October", "last", "year", "to", "form", "the", "All", "Basotho", "Convention", "-LRB-", "ABC", "-RRB-", ",", "crossing", "the", "floor", "with", "17", "members", "of", "parliament", ",", "causing", "constitutional", "monarch", "King", "Letsie", "III", "to", "dissolve", "parliament", "and", "call", "the", "snap", "election", "."], "subj_start": 10, "subj_end": 12, "obj_start": 0, "obj_end": 1, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "-LRB-", "NNP", "-RRB-", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 3, 0, 5, 3, 7, 3, 9, 3, 13, 13, 13, 9, 15, 13, 15, 3, 3, 20, 18, 23, 23, 18, 25, 23, 3, 3, 32, 32, 32, 32, 27, 34, 27, 34, 34, 34, 40, 40, 37, 3], "stanford_deprel": ["compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "case", "nmod", "amod", "nmod:tmod", "mark", "xcomp", "det", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "appos", "punct", "punct", "xcomp", "det", "dobj", "case", "nummod", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct", "xcomp", "amod", "compound", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "mark", "xcomp", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "det", "compound", "dobj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [3, 1, 0, 7, 7, 7, 3, 9, 3, 11, 0, 11, 11, 11, 11, 3, 3, 3, 20, 18, 23, 23, 18, 25, 23, 3, 3, 29, 30, 0, 30, 30, 34, 27, 34, 37, 3, 40, 40, 37, 40]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9b7111c4ca4", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20071026.0056.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["In", "1983", ",", "a", "year", "after", "the", "rally", ",", "Forsberg", "received", "the", "so-called", "``", "genius", "award", "''", "from", "the", "John", "D.", "and", "Catherine", "T.", "MacArthur", "Foundation", "."], "subj_start": 9, "subj_end": 9, "obj_start": 19, "obj_end": 20, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "``", "NN", "NN", "''", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "DATE", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 11, 11, 5, 11, 8, 8, 5, 11, 11, 0, 16, 16, 16, 16, 11, 16, 21, 21, 21, 16, 21, 26, 26, 26, 21, 11], "stanford_deprel": ["case", "nmod", "punct", "det", "nmod:tmod", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "punct", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "cc", "compound", "compound", "compound", "conj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 11, 11, 5, 8, 5, 8, 11, 11, 11, 0, 18, 18, 18, 18, 11, 18, 21, 18, 21, 22, 22, 22, 25, 25, 25, 22]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9aeb61c81e7", "docid": "eng-NG-31-126955-9171242", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["This", "was", "among", "a", "batch", "of", "paperback", "Oxford", "World", "'s", "Classics", "that", "I", "was", "given", "as", "a", "reward", "for", "reading", "and", "commenting", "on", "a", "manuscript", "for", "OUP", "."], "subj_start": 26, "subj_end": 26, "obj_start": 7, "obj_end": 8, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [5, 5, 5, 5, 0, 11, 9, 9, 11, 9, 5, 15, 15, 15, 5, 18, 18, 15, 20, 18, 15, 15, 25, 25, 22, 27, 25, 5], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubj", "cop", "case", "det", "ROOT", "case", "compound", "compound", "nmod:poss", "case", "nmod", "mark", "nsubjpass", "auxpass", "dep", "case", "det", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "cc", "conj", "case", "det", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 0, 8, 5, 8, 5, 8, 2, 8, 8, 8, 15, 15, 15, 8, 18, 18, 15, 18, 19, 20, 20, 25, 25, 20, 27, 25, 27]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9c9956eccbc", "docid": "APW_ENG_20100119.0780", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "latest", "investigation", "was", "authorized", "after", "the", "Supreme", "Court", "in", "2007", "found", "DCC", "and", "its", "founder", ",", "Jim", "Flavin", ",", "guilty", "of", "selling", "DCC", "'s", "-LRB-", "EURO", "-RRB-", "106", "million", "-LRB-", "then", "$", "130", "million", "-RRB-", "stake", "in", "Fyffes", "after", "Flavin", "--", "also", "a", "Fyffes", "director", "at", "the", "time", "--", "received", "inside", "information", "about", "bad", "Fyffes", "news", "in", "the", "pipeline", "."], "subj_start": 55, "subj_end": 55, "obj_start": 28, "obj_end": 29, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "NUMBER", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "POS", "-LRB-", "NN", "-RRB-", "CD", "CD", "-LRB-", "RB", "$", "CD", "CD", "-RRB-", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ":", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "DATE", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "MONEY", "MONEY", "MONEY", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [3, 3, 5, 5, 0, 9, 9, 9, 5, 11, 5, 5, 21, 13, 16, 13, 16, 19, 16, 16, 12, 23, 21, 23, 24, 27, 24, 27, 30, 27, 33, 33, 27, 35, 33, 33, 27, 39, 37, 41, 37, 27, 46, 46, 46, 24, 49, 49, 46, 5, 5, 53, 51, 57, 57, 57, 53, 60, 60, 57, 5], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "amod", "nsubjpass", "auxpass", "ROOT", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "dep", "nsubj", "cc", "nmod:poss", "conj", "punct", "compound", "appos", "punct", "xcomp", "mark", "advcl", "dobj", "case", "punct", "dep", "punct", "compound", "nummod", "punct", "advmod", "dep", "compound", "nummod", "punct", "dep", "case", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct", "advmod", "det", "compound", "acl:relcl", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "dep", "case", "nmod", "case", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [3, 3, 5, 5, 0, 12, 8, 12, 8, 11, 12, 5, 12, 13, 16, 18, 18, 13, 18, 12, 12, 23, 12, 23, 24, 24, 24, 24, 24, 29, 29, 37, 29, 33, 33, 29, 29, 39, 37, 51, 51, 41, 46, 46, 46, 41, 49, 49, 46, 51, 5, 53, 51, 57, 57, 57, 53, 60, 60, 57, 60]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9197aba87ff", "docid": "APW_ENG_20070501.0905.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "event", "is", "a", "response", "to", "a", "White", "House", "immigration", "reform", "proposal", "in", "March", ",", "said", "Chung-Wha", "Hong", ",", "executive", "director", "of", "the", "New", "York", "Immigration", "Coalition", "."], "subj_start": 23, "subj_end": 26, "obj_start": 13, "obj_end": 13, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "DATE", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 5, 5, 5, 16, 12, 12, 12, 12, 12, 12, 5, 14, 12, 16, 0, 18, 16, 18, 21, 18, 27, 27, 27, 27, 27, 21, 16], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "nsubj", "cop", "det", "ccomp", "case", "det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct", "ROOT", "compound", "nsubj", "punct", "amod", "appos", "case", "det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 5, 5, 5, 0, 12, 12, 12, 8, 11, 12, 5, 14, 12, 5, 5, 17, 17, 17, 23, 17, 29, 29, 29, 26, 29, 23, 29]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb94b342e4da3", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20071105.0397.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Manning", "was", "prime", "minister", "in", "1991", ",", "and", "called", "a", "snap", "elections", "in", "1995", "which", "he", "lost", "to", "the", "UNC", "after", "the", "party", "entered", "an", "electoral", "arrangement", "with", "the", "National", "Alliance", "for", "Reconstruction", "."], "subj_start": 19, "subj_end": 19, "obj_start": 29, "obj_end": 32, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["VBG", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [4, 4, 4, 0, 6, 4, 4, 4, 4, 12, 12, 9, 14, 9, 17, 17, 9, 20, 20, 17, 24, 23, 24, 17, 27, 27, 24, 31, 31, 31, 27, 33, 27, 4], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubj", "cop", "amod", "ROOT", "case", "nmod", "punct", "cc", "conj", "det", "compound", "xcomp", "case", "nmod", "dobj", "nsubj", "ccomp", "case", "det", "nmod", "mark", "det", "nsubj", "advcl", "det", "amod", "dobj", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 0, 4, 2, 6, 2, 2, 9, 2, 12, 12, 0, 14, 9, 17, 17, 2, 20, 20, 17, 24, 23, 24, 2, 27, 27, 24, 30, 30, 27, 30, 30, 30, 30]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9062d316790", "docid": "eng-NG-31-142407-10043754", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Christine", "Egerszegi-Obrist", "-LRB-", "l", "-RRB-", "and", "Haddad-Adel"], "subj_start": 6, "subj_end": 6, "obj_start": 0, "obj_end": 1, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "-LRB-", "NN", "-RRB-", "CC", "NNP"], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 0, 4, 2, 4, 2, 2], "stanford_deprel": ["compound", "ROOT", "punct", "appos", "punct", "cc", "conj"], "ucca_heads": [0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 9]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb919cf88f14e", "docid": "eng-NG-31-142686-10071439", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Al-Hubayshi", "explained", "that", ",", "far", "from", "being", "a", "mastermind", ",", "Abu", "Zubaydah", "was", "responsible", "for", "``", "receiving", "people", "and", "financing", "the", "camp", ",", "''", "that", "he", "once", "bought", "him", "travel", "tickets", ",", "and", "that", "he", "was", "the", "man", "he", "went", "to", "when", "he", "needed", "a", "replacement", "passport", "."], "subj_start": 42, "subj_end": 42, "obj_start": 25, "obj_end": 25, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "``", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "''", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 0, 14, 14, 9, 9, 9, 9, 14, 14, 12, 14, 14, 2, 17, 17, 14, 17, 17, 17, 22, 20, 2, 23, 28, 28, 28, 24, 28, 28, 30, 30, 30, 38, 38, 38, 38, 30, 40, 38, 44, 44, 44, 40, 47, 47, 44, 28], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubj", "ROOT", "mark", "punct", "advmod", "mark", "cop", "det", "advcl", "punct", "compound", "nsubj", "cop", "ccomp", "mark", "punct", "advcl", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "det", "dobj", "punct", "root", "mark", "nsubj", "advmod", "root", "dobj", "dep", "dobj", "punct", "cc", "mark", "nsubj", "cop", "det", "conj", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "mark", "advmod", "nsubj", "advcl", "det", "compound", "dobj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [1, 0, 9, 9, 9, 7, 16, 11, 9, 16, 16, 13, 16, 4, 19, 19, 16, 19, 19, 19, 24, 22, 4, 4, 30, 30, 30, 4, 30, 33, 30, 30, 38, 38, 38, 30, 40, 38, 42, 40, 42, 46, 46, 42, 49, 49, 46, 49]}
{"id": "61b3a89f60d0777c9f0f", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174587-12962011", "relation": "per:employee_of", "token": ["Olivia", "Palermo", "was", "looking", "very", "Blair", "Waldorfish", "at", "last", "week", "'s", "You", "Know", "You", "Want", "It", ":", "Style-Inspiration-Confidence", "book", "launch", ",", "so", "it", "'s", "only", "fitting", "she", "ran", "into", "real-life", "Gossip", "Girl", "s", "Leighton", "Meester", "and", "Nicole", "Fiscella", "on", "her", "way", "there", "!"], "subj_start": 0, "subj_end": 1, "obj_start": 30, "obj_end": 31, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "PRP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 4, 4, 0, 7, 7, 4, 10, 10, 4, 10, 10, 12, 15, 13, 15, 13, 20, 20, 13, 20, 26, 26, 26, 26, 20, 28, 26, 32, 32, 32, 28, 35, 35, 26, 35, 38, 35, 41, 41, 35, 35, 10], "stanford_deprel": ["compound", "nsubj", "aux", "ROOT", "advmod", "compound", "dobj", "case", "amod", "nmod", "case", "dep", "dep", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "dobj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "dep", "punct", "mark", "nsubj", "cop", "advmod", "advcl", "nsubj", "ccomp", "case", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "compound", "compound", "nmod:tmod", "cc", "compound", "conj", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "advmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [4, 1, 4, 0, 4, 4, 6, 12, 10, 12, 10, 4, 12, 12, 12, 12, 12, 12, 12, 12, 4, 37, 37, 37, 37, 37, 32, 37, 32, 40, 4, 37, 32, 32, 40, 40, 40, 43, 47, 47, 32, 47, 47]}
{"id": "61b3aa9e363a44f45c48", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20100414.0728", "relation": "org:alternate_names", "token": ["But", "US", "and", "Indian", "experts", "say", "it", "has", "hesitated", "to", "take", "action", "against", "Lashkar-e-Taiba", ",", "which", "means", "``", "The", "Army", "of", "the", "Pure", ",", "''", "believing", "that", "the", "Islamic", "militants", "could", "prove", "useful", "in", "pressuring", "its", "historic", "rival", "India", "."], "subj_start": 13, "subj_end": 13, "obj_start": 19, "obj_end": 22, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["CC", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "``", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [6, 6, 2, 5, 2, 0, 9, 9, 6, 11, 9, 11, 14, 11, 14, 17, 14, 17, 20, 17, 23, 23, 20, 6, 6, 6, 32, 30, 30, 32, 32, 26, 32, 35, 32, 39, 39, 39, 35, 6], "stanford_deprel": ["cc", "nsubj", "cc", "amod", "conj", "ROOT", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "mark", "xcomp", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "punct", "det", "dobj", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "punct", "xcomp", "mark", "det", "amod", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "xcomp", "mark", "advcl", "nmod:poss", "amod", "amod", "dobj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [30, 5, 2, 2, 6, 0, 9, 9, 6, 11, 9, 11, 14, 14, 14, 21, 14, 21, 24, 21, 24, 24, 24, 6, 6, 6, 37, 34, 34, 37, 37, 37, 30, 39, 37, 43, 43, 43, 39, 43]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb92c8c9d3d94", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20100628.0710", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["``", "I", "have", "n't", "the", "slightest", "doubt", "that", "as", "soon", "as", "US", "and", "Israeli", "warships", "are", "in", "place", "...", "and", "attempt", "to", "inspect", "the", "first", "-LRB-", "Iranian", "-RRB-", "merchant", "ship", ",", "a", "shower", "of", "projectiles", "will", "be", "unleashed", "...", "That", "will", "be", "the", "exact", "moment", "the", "terrible", "war", "will", "start", ",", "''", "Castro", "wrote", "in", "the", "Cubadebate", "website", "."], "subj_start": 52, "subj_end": 52, "obj_start": 26, "obj_end": 26, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "NATIONALITY", "stanford_pos": ["``", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ":", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "-LRB-", "JJ", "-RRB-", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ":", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "''", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORDINAL", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [0, 7, 7, 7, 7, 7, 1, 54, 10, 45, 18, 15, 12, 12, 18, 18, 18, 10, 10, 10, 38, 23, 21, 30, 30, 30, 30, 30, 30, 23, 21, 33, 38, 35, 33, 38, 38, 10, 45, 45, 45, 45, 45, 45, 54, 48, 48, 50, 50, 45, 54, 54, 54, 7, 58, 58, 58, 54, 7], "stanford_deprel": ["ROOT", "nsubj", "aux", "neg", "det", "amod", "root", "mark", "advmod", "advmod", "mark", "compound", "cc", "conj", "nsubj", "cop", "case", "advcl", "punct", "cc", "dep", "mark", "acl", "det", "amod", "punct", "amod", "punct", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "det", "nsubjpass", "case", "nmod", "aux", "auxpass", "conj", "punct", "nsubj", "aux", "cop", "det", "amod", "ccomp", "det", "amod", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "punct", "punct", "nsubj", "ccomp", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [3, 3, 0, 3, 7, 7, 3, 15, 15, 9, 9, 16, 12, 12, 0, 3, 18, 16, 3, 23, 23, 23, 3, 30, 30, 30, 30, 30, 30, 23, 3, 33, 38, 35, 33, 38, 38, 3, 3, 42, 42, 3, 45, 45, 54, 48, 48, 50, 50, 42, 42, 42, 54, 42, 58, 58, 58, 54, 58]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb97b15e6512b", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20090707.0058", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["In", "O'Brien", "'s", "home", "just", "off", "Broadway", "in", "Saratoga", "Springs", ",", "there", "are", "shelves", "of", "books", "that", "mention", "his", "association", "with", "Balanchine", "as", "well", "as", "Jerome", "Robbins", ",", "Anthony", "Tudor", ",", "Rudolf", "Nureyev", "and", "Mikhail", "Baryshnikov", ",", "among", "others", "."], "subj_start": 25, "subj_end": 26, "obj_start": 6, "obj_end": 6, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "LOCATION", "stanford_pos": ["IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [4, 4, 2, 13, 7, 7, 4, 10, 10, 7, 13, 13, 0, 13, 16, 14, 18, 14, 20, 18, 22, 20, 22, 23, 23, 27, 22, 27, 30, 27, 27, 33, 27, 27, 36, 27, 22, 39, 22, 13], "stanford_deprel": ["case", "nmod:poss", "case", "nmod", "advmod", "advmod", "nmod", "case", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "expl", "ROOT", "nsubj", "case", "nmod", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "nmod:poss", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "cc", "mwe", "mwe", "compound", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "compound", "conj", "punct", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [4, 4, 2, 13, 7, 7, 4, 9, 4, 9, 13, 13, 0, 16, 14, 13, 18, 16, 20, 18, 22, 20, 20, 23, 23, 20, 26, 26, 26, 29, 26, 26, 32, 26, 26, 35, 20, 39, 20, 39]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb912289c20ad", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20080504.0041.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Folded", "into", "Dillinger", "'s", "office", ",", "the", "program", "is", "headed", "by", "director", "Duncan", "McCormack", ",", "a", "51-year-old", "with", "a", "diverse", "background", "that", "includes", "mental", "health", "counseling", "."], "subj_start": 2, "subj_end": 2, "obj_start": 11, "obj_end": 11, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "TITLE", "stanford_pos": ["VBN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [10, 5, 5, 3, 1, 10, 8, 10, 10, 0, 14, 14, 14, 10, 14, 17, 14, 21, 21, 21, 17, 23, 21, 26, 26, 23, 10], "stanford_deprel": ["advcl", "case", "nmod:poss", "case", "nmod", "punct", "det", "nsubjpass", "auxpass", "ROOT", "case", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "det", "appos", "case", "det", "amod", "nmod", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [0, 5, 5, 3, 1, 1, 8, 0, 10, 1, 13, 13, 10, 13, 13, 19, 20, 13, 23, 23, 20, 25, 23, 27, 28, 25, 28]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9d5d39c51ce", "docid": "bolt-eng-DF-170-181109-55859", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["So", "let", "me", "get", "this", "straight", "-", "Murat", "Kurnaz", "should", "have", "been", "shot", "in", "2001", "because", "I", "asked", "you", "if", "he", "should", "be", "shot", "for", "being", "German", "in", "2009", "?"], "subj_start": 20, "subj_end": 20, "obj_start": 14, "obj_end": 14, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "DATE", "stanford_pos": ["RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "DATE", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 0, 4, 2, 13, 13, 13, 9, 13, 13, 13, 13, 4, 15, 4, 18, 18, 2, 18, 24, 24, 24, 24, 18, 27, 27, 24, 29, 27, 2], "stanford_deprel": ["advmod", "ROOT", "nsubj", "ccomp", "det", "dep", "punct", "compound", "nsubjpass", "aux", "aux", "auxpass", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "mark", "nsubj", "advcl", "dobj", "mark", "nsubjpass", "aux", "auxpass", "advcl", "mark", "cop", "advcl", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [13, 0, 2, 2, 4, 4, 2, 2, 2, 13, 13, 13, 2, 15, 13, 18, 18, 2, 18, 24, 24, 24, 24, 18, 26, 24, 26, 29, 26, 29]}
{"id": "61b3a0af8f529cfaab32", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174587-12962613", "relation": "per:cities_of_residence", "token": ["Spencer", "Pratt", ":", "Beverly", "Hills", "Birthday", "Boy"], "subj_start": 0, "subj_end": 1, "obj_start": 3, "obj_end": 4, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "CITY", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN"], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 0, 2, 7, 7, 7, 2], "stanford_deprel": ["compound", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "dep"], "ucca_heads": [0, 1, 1, 7, 4, 7, 1]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9d234f9bf31", "docid": "eng-NG-31-141586-9960082", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["While", "the", "Massachusetts", "House", "of", "Representatives", "debates", "the", "Global", "Warming", "Solutions", "Act", ",", "please", "show", "that", "commitment", ",", "by", "publicly", "calling", "for", "strong", "near", "-", "and", "long-term", "reductions", "in", "global", "warming", "pollution", "covering", "all", "areas", "including", "utilities", ",", "transportation", ",", "and", "more", "."], "subj_start": 2, "subj_end": 5, "obj_start": 8, "obj_end": 11, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "MISC", "stanford_pos": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNP", ",", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", ":", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "RBR", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "MISC", "MISC", "MISC", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [7, 4, 4, 7, 6, 4, 14, 12, 12, 12, 12, 7, 14, 0, 14, 15, 16, 17, 21, 21, 17, 21, 22, 28, 28, 28, 28, 23, 32, 32, 32, 28, 28, 35, 33, 37, 35, 37, 37, 37, 37, 37, 14], "stanford_deprel": ["mark", "det", "compound", "nsubj", "case", "nmod", "advcl", "det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "ROOT", "dobj", "dep", "dep", "punct", "mark", "advmod", "acl", "advcl", "xcomp", "case", "punct", "cc", "amod", "nmod", "case", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "acl", "det", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "punct", "conj", "punct", "cc", "conj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [15, 4, 4, 7, 6, 4, 0, 12, 12, 9, 12, 7, 7, 15, 7, 17, 15, 7, 21, 21, 7, 30, 24, 30, 24, 24, 24, 21, 34, 33, 34, 30, 34, 37, 35, 39, 37, 39, 39, 39, 39, 39, 39]}
{"id": "61b3a9d0d12e113c74d9", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20070524.0198.LDC2009T13", "relation": "per:children", "token": ["Besides", "his", "son", "Charles", ",", "an", "author", "and", "journalist", ",", "Kaiser", "is", "survived", "by", "his", "wife", "of", "67", "years", ",", "Hannah", "Greeley", "Kaiser", ";", "two", "other", "sons", ",", "Robert", "G", ",", "a", "former", "managing", "editor", "and", "now", "an", "associate", "editor", "of", "The", "Washington", "Post", ",", "and", "David", ",", "a", "professor", "of", "history", "at", "the", "Naval", "War", "College", "in", "Newport", ",", "RI", ";", "and", "four", "grandchildren", "."], "subj_start": 10, "subj_end": 10, "obj_start": 28, "obj_end": 29, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", ":", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [4, 4, 4, 13, 4, 7, 4, 7, 7, 4, 13, 13, 0, 16, 16, 13, 19, 19, 13, 13, 23, 23, 20, 23, 27, 27, 23, 27, 30, 27, 30, 35, 35, 35, 30, 35, 40, 40, 40, 35, 44, 44, 44, 40, 30, 30, 30, 47, 50, 47, 52, 50, 57, 57, 57, 57, 50, 59, 57, 59, 59, 23, 23, 65, 23, 23], "stanford_deprel": ["case", "nmod:poss", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "det", "appos", "cc", "conj", "punct", "nsubjpass", "auxpass", "ROOT", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "case", "nummod", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "compound", "root", "punct", "nummod", "amod", "conj", "punct", "compound", "appos", "punct", "det", "amod", "compound", "appos", "cc", "advmod", "det", "amod", "conj", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "cc", "conj", "punct", "det", "appos", "case", "nmod", "case", "det", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "cc", "nummod", "conj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [0, 1, 1, 0, 4, 13, 13, 7, 7, 13, 13, 13, 4, 21, 16, 4, 19, 19, 16, 4, 13, 21, 21, 4, 27, 27, 4, 4, 1, 29, 37, 35, 35, 35, 37, 37, 4, 40, 40, 4, 42, 40, 42, 42, 40, 40, 40, 47, 50, 65, 52, 50, 57, 57, 57, 57, 65, 59, 57, 59, 59, 65, 65, 65, 47, 65]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb994a6170efd", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20070404.0020.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["It", "says", "that", "in", "2005", "Sohail", "``", "was", "visited", "by", "a", "Jackson", "Hewitt", "Tax", "Services", "Inc.", "employee", ",", "who", "informed", "Sohail", "that", "Santa", "Barbara", "Bank", "had", "told", "Jackson", "Hewitt", "corporate", "headquarters", "that", "Sohail", "'s", "Smart", "Tax/Jackson", "Hewitt", "stores", "were", "filing", "too", "many", "fraudulent", "returns", ".", "''"], "subj_start": 11, "subj_end": 15, "obj_start": 4, "obj_end": 4, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "DATE", "stanford_pos": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "``", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ".", "''"], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 0, 9, 6, 6, 9, 9, 9, 2, 17, 17, 17, 17, 17, 17, 17, 9, 17, 20, 17, 20, 27, 25, 25, 27, 27, 20, 31, 31, 31, 27, 40, 38, 33, 38, 38, 38, 40, 40, 27, 42, 44, 44, 40, 2, 2], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubj", "ROOT", "mark", "case", "nummod", "nmod", "punct", "auxpass", "ccomp", "case", "det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "dobj", "mark", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "compound", "compound", "amod", "dobj", "mark", "nmod:poss", "case", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "advmod", "amod", "amod", "dobj", "punct", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 0, 9, 5, 9, 9, 9, 9, 2, 17, 17, 17, 12, 12, 12, 12, 9, 17, 20, 17, 20, 27, 27, 23, 23, 27, 20, 31, 28, 31, 27, 42, 40, 33, 40, 35, 38, 42, 42, 27, 44, 46, 46, 42, 46, 46]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb93994c6f492", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20070617.0384.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Much", "to", "the", "delight", "of", "American", "hip-hop", "star", "Pharrell", "Williams", ",", "who", "watched", "the", "race", "alongside", "Hamilton", "'s", "father", "Anthony", ",", "Hamilton", "opened", "up", "a", "2.2", "sec", "lead", "from", "Alonso", "after", "ten", "laps", "with", "Massa", "4.5", "sec", "behind", "."], "subj_start": 16, "subj_end": 16, "obj_start": 26, "obj_end": 26, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "PERSON", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [0, 4, 4, 1, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 4, 10, 13, 10, 15, 13, 20, 20, 17, 20, 15, 20, 23, 20, 23, 28, 28, 28, 23, 30, 28, 33, 33, 23, 37, 37, 37, 33, 33, 1], "stanford_deprel": ["ROOT", "case", "det", "nmod", "case", "amod", "amod", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "det", "dobj", "case", "nmod:poss", "case", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "compound:prt", "det", "nummod", "compound", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "case", "nummod", "nmod", "case", "compound", "nummod", "nmod", "advmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [25, 1, 4, 0, 11, 10, 10, 11, 4, 11, 11, 15, 11, 17, 15, 22, 22, 19, 22, 15, 4, 25, 4, 25, 30, 29, 30, 25, 32, 25, 35, 35, 25, 40, 40, 39, 40, 4, 40]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9ebac81f0e3", "docid": "XIN_ENG_20080324.0170.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["DAMASCUS", "--", "Saudi", "permanent", "representative", "to", "the", "Arab", "League", "-LRB-", "AL", "-RRB-", "Ahmad", "Qattan", "said", "here", "Monday", "that", "he", "will", "attend", "the", "upcoming", "Arab", "summit", "on", "behalf", "of", "his", "country", ",", "ruling", "out", "the", "presence", "of", "Saudi", "King", "Abdullah", "or", "Foreign", "Minister", "Prince", "Saud", "al-Faisal", "."], "subj_start": 12, "subj_end": 13, "obj_start": 36, "obj_end": 36, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "NATIONALITY", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "-LRB-", "NNP", "-RRB-", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "stanford_head": [0, 1, 5, 5, 15, 9, 9, 9, 5, 11, 9, 11, 14, 9, 1, 15, 15, 21, 21, 21, 15, 25, 25, 25, 21, 27, 25, 30, 30, 27, 21, 21, 32, 35, 32, 39, 39, 39, 35, 39, 45, 45, 45, 45, 39, 1], "stanford_deprel": ["ROOT", "punct", "compound", "amod", "nsubj", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "compound", "dep", "parataxis", "advmod", "nmod:tmod", "mark", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "det", "amod", "amod", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "punct", "advcl", "compound:prt", "det", "dobj", "case", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "cc", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "conj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [0, 15, 5, 5, 15, 8, 8, 5, 8, 8, 8, 15, 15, 13, 0, 17, 15, 21, 21, 21, 15, 25, 25, 25, 21, 27, 21, 30, 30, 27, 15, 15, 35, 35, 32, 39, 38, 43, 35, 43, 42, 43, 15, 43, 43, 43]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb935d4998f13", "docid": "WPB_ENG_20100127.0044", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "Super", "Bowl", "is", "getting", ",", "in", "addition", "to", "some", "Saints", ",", "a", "controversial", "dose", "of", "the", "culture", "wars", ":", "Florida", "quarterback", "prodigy", "Tim", "Tebow", "will", "appear", "in", "a", "30-second", "ad", "purchased", "by", "the", "conservative", "group", "Focus", "on", "the", "Family", "that", "is", "scheduled", "to", "air", "during", "the", "nation", "'s", "biggest", "football", "game", "on", "Feb.", "7", "on", "CBS", "."], "subj_start": 36, "subj_end": 39, "obj_start": 56, "obj_end": 56, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ":", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "MISC", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [3, 3, 5, 5, 0, 5, 8, 5, 11, 11, 8, 11, 15, 15, 11, 19, 19, 19, 15, 5, 25, 25, 25, 25, 27, 27, 5, 31, 31, 31, 27, 31, 37, 37, 37, 37, 32, 40, 40, 37, 43, 43, 37, 45, 43, 52, 48, 52, 48, 52, 52, 43, 54, 52, 54, 57, 54, 5], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "ROOT", "punct", "case", "nmod", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "det", "amod", "appos", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "parataxis", "case", "det", "amod", "nmod", "acl", "case", "det", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "case", "det", "nmod", "nsubjpass", "auxpass", "acl:relcl", "case", "nmod", "case", "det", "nmod:poss", "case", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "nummod", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [3, 3, 5, 5, 0, 5, 27, 7, 7, 11, 5, 5, 15, 15, 19, 15, 19, 19, 5, 5, 23, 23, 24, 27, 24, 27, 5, 32, 31, 31, 32, 27, 36, 36, 36, 32, 36, 37, 37, 37, 43, 43, 32, 45, 43, 52, 48, 52, 48, 52, 52, 45, 54, 45, 54, 57, 45, 57]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb97b41e3c59d", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20081218.0113.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "two", "Bush", "administrations", "snubbed", "highly", "qualified", "Northwest", "Republicans", "--", "Dan", "Evans", ",", "Jennifer", "Dunn", "and", "Slade", "Gorton", "--", "and", "were", "satisfied", "with", "making", "prominent", "GOP", "donors", "into", "U.S.", "ambassadors", "to", "diplomatic", "backwaters", "."], "subj_start": 13, "subj_end": 14, "obj_start": 28, "obj_end": 28, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "COUNTRY", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNPS", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "NUMBER", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [4, 4, 4, 5, 0, 7, 9, 9, 5, 9, 12, 9, 12, 15, 12, 12, 18, 12, 9, 5, 22, 5, 24, 22, 27, 27, 24, 30, 30, 24, 33, 33, 24, 5], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "nummod", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "advmod", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "compound", "dep", "punct", "compound", "conj", "cc", "compound", "conj", "punct", "cc", "auxpass", "conj", "mark", "advcl", "amod", "compound", "dobj", "case", "compound", "nmod", "case", "amod", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 9, 9, 5, 9, 9, 11, 11, 11, 14, 11, 11, 17, 5, 22, 22, 5, 24, 22, 27, 27, 24, 30, 30, 24, 33, 33, 30, 33]}
{"id": "61b3a9d0d1a18d8b6d76", "docid": "eng-NG-31-145805-10296359", "relation": "per:children", "token": ["*", "Britney", "Spears", "'", "Sunday", "with", "her", "kids", "*", "Sunday", "was", "Britney", "'s", "day", "with", "Sean", ",", "2", ",", "and", "Jayden", ",", "1", ",", "and", "she", "took", "them", "to", "lunch", "at", "Taverna", "Tony", "'s", "in", "Malibu", ",", "a", "Greek", "restaurant", "."], "subj_start": 11, "subj_end": 11, "obj_start": 20, "obj_end": 20, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["SYM", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "SYM", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "PERSON", "O", "DURATION", "O", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [5, 3, 5, 3, 14, 8, 8, 5, 10, 14, 14, 14, 12, 0, 16, 14, 16, 16, 14, 14, 14, 21, 21, 21, 21, 27, 21, 27, 30, 27, 33, 33, 27, 33, 36, 33, 21, 40, 40, 21, 14], "stanford_deprel": ["dep", "compound", "nmod:poss", "case", "nsubj", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "dep", "nmod:tmod", "cop", "nmod:poss", "case", "ROOT", "case", "nmod", "punct", "nummod", "punct", "cc", "conj", "punct", "amod", "punct", "cc", "nsubj", "conj", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "case", "compound", "nmod", "case", "case", "nmod", "punct", "det", "amod", "appos", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [30, 5, 0, 30, 30, 8, 8, 30, 30, 30, 30, 14, 12, 30, 16, 14, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16, 21, 21, 30, 30, 30, 30, 30, 30, 0, 32, 30, 32, 32, 36, 32, 36, 40, 40, 36, 40]}
{"id": "61b3a89f60cb83f37693", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174611-12980643", "relation": "per:employee_of", "token": ["Donald", "Wildmon", ",", "the", "founder", "and", "head", "of", "the", "American", "Family", "Association", ",", "is", "asking", "its", "members", "to", "petition", "Congress", "to", "end", "all", "funding", "for", "PBS", "."], "subj_start": 0, "subj_end": 1, "obj_start": 9, "obj_end": 11, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 15, 2, 5, 2, 5, 5, 12, 12, 12, 12, 5, 2, 15, 0, 17, 15, 19, 15, 19, 22, 19, 24, 22, 26, 24, 15], "stanford_deprel": ["compound", "nsubj", "punct", "det", "appos", "cc", "conj", "case", "det", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "aux", "ROOT", "nmod:poss", "dobj", "mark", "xcomp", "dobj", "mark", "xcomp", "det", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [5, 1, 5, 0, 0, 5, 5, 7, 5, 5, 10, 10, 5, 5, 5, 17, 5, 19, 5, 19, 22, 19, 24, 22, 26, 24, 26]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb96dba31ff1d", "docid": "LTW_ENG_20070103.0149.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["But", ",", "as", "a", "Zionist", ",", "he", "insisted", "that", "the", "city", "remain", "under", "Israeli", "sovereignty", ",", "rejecting", "Palestinians", "'", "demand", "to", "make", "its", "Arab", "part", "the", "capital", "of", "their", "would-be", "state", "."], "subj_start": 6, "subj_end": 6, "obj_start": 23, "obj_end": 23, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "MISC", "stanford_pos": ["CC", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNPS", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [8, 8, 5, 5, 8, 8, 8, 0, 12, 11, 12, 8, 15, 15, 12, 12, 12, 20, 18, 17, 22, 20, 25, 25, 27, 27, 22, 31, 31, 31, 27, 8], "stanford_deprel": ["cc", "punct", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "mark", "det", "nsubj", "ccomp", "case", "amod", "nmod", "punct", "xcomp", "nmod:poss", "case", "dobj", "mark", "acl", "nmod:poss", "compound", "nsubj", "det", "xcomp", "case", "nmod:poss", "amod", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [0, 22, 5, 5, 22, 22, 1, 22, 12, 12, 12, 8, 15, 15, 8, 8, 8, 20, 20, 8, 1, 0, 25, 25, 22, 27, 22, 33, 33, 33, 27, 33]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9149334e732", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174587-12962444", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["This", "Friday", "-LRB-", "September", "11th", "-RRB-", ",", "Frankie", "Delgado", "from", "The", "Hills", ",", "Zack", "Taylor", ",", "and", "another", "very", "special", "guest", "will", "be", "partying", "at", "Club", "Se7en", "in", "Niagara", "Falls", ",", "Ontario", "!!"], "subj_start": 7, "subj_end": 8, "obj_start": 3, "obj_end": 4, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "DATE", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NNP", "-LRB-", "NNP", "JJ", "-RRB-", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "IN"], "stanford_ner": ["DATE", "DATE", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "NUMBER"], "stanford_head": [24, 24, 4, 2, 4, 4, 24, 9, 24, 12, 12, 9, 12, 15, 12, 12, 9, 21, 20, 21, 9, 24, 24, 0, 27, 27, 24, 30, 30, 27, 30, 30, 24], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubj", "dep", "punct", "dep", "amod", "punct", "punct", "compound", "nsubj", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "appos", "punct", "cc", "det", "advmod", "amod", "conj", "aux", "aux", "ROOT", "case", "compound", "nmod", "case", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "appos", "advmod"], "ucca_heads": [2, 24, 24, 24, 4, 24, 24, 24, 8, 11, 8, 11, 8, 8, 14, 8, 8, 21, 20, 21, 8, 24, 24, 0, 26, 24, 26, 29, 26, 29, 29, 29, 29]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb92708602e74", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174611-12973922", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Labels", ":", "``", "celibacy", "''", ",", "Brandon", "McInerney", ",", "California", ",", "gay", "youth", ",", "hate", "crimes", ",", "Lawrence", "King", ",", "murder", ",", "transgender", "issues"], "subj_start": 6, "subj_end": 7, "obj_start": 14, "obj_end": 15, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "CRIMINAL_CHARGE", "stanford_pos": ["NNS", ":", "``", "NN", "''", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS"], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [0, 1, 4, 15, 4, 4, 8, 4, 8, 8, 8, 13, 8, 8, 1, 15, 15, 19, 15, 19, 19, 19, 24, 19], "stanford_deprel": ["ROOT", "punct", "punct", "nsubj", "punct", "punct", "compound", "appos", "punct", "appos", "punct", "amod", "appos", "punct", "dep", "dobj", "punct", "compound", "dep", "punct", "appos", "punct", "amod", "appos"], "ucca_heads": [0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 7, 7, 7, 7, 13, 7, 7, 16, 7, 7, 7, 18, 7, 7, 7, 24, 7]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9619d933e75", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20080427.0022.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["In", "a", "statement", ",", "the", "Ontario", "Human", "Rights", "Commission", "said", "the", "contents", "of", "press", "articles", "were", "beyond", "its", "purview", ",", "but", "added", "it", "``", "has", "serious", "concerns", "about", "the", "content", "of", "a", "number", "of", "articles", "concerning", "Muslims", "''", "published", "by", "Maclean", "'s", "and", "other", "media", "outlets", "which", "were", "``", "identified", "as", "contributing", "to", "Islamophobia", "and", "promoting", "societal", "intolerance", "towards", "Muslims", ".", "''"], "subj_start": 5, "subj_end": 8, "obj_start": 40, "obj_end": 40, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "``", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNPS", "''", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "``", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", ".", "''"], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [3, 3, 10, 10, 9, 9, 9, 9, 10, 0, 12, 19, 15, 15, 12, 19, 19, 19, 10, 10, 10, 10, 25, 25, 22, 27, 25, 30, 30, 27, 33, 33, 30, 35, 33, 35, 36, 37, 37, 41, 39, 41, 41, 46, 46, 41, 50, 50, 50, 46, 52, 50, 54, 52, 52, 52, 58, 56, 60, 58, 10, 10], "stanford_deprel": ["case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "nsubj", "case", "compound", "nmod", "cop", "case", "nmod:poss", "ccomp", "punct", "cc", "conj", "nsubj", "punct", "ccomp", "amod", "dobj", "case", "det", "nmod", "case", "det", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "acl", "dobj", "punct", "acl", "case", "nmod", "case", "cc", "amod", "compound", "conj", "nsubjpass", "auxpass", "punct", "acl:relcl", "mark", "advcl", "case", "nmod", "cc", "conj", "amod", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "punct", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [3, 3, 10, 10, 9, 9, 9, 9, 10, 0, 12, 19, 19, 19, 0, 19, 19, 19, 10, 10, 22, 10, 25, 25, 22, 25, 25, 30, 30, 25, 35, 33, 35, 33, 30, 35, 36, 10, 19, 41, 19, 41, 41, 46, 46, 0, 50, 50, 50, 10, 52, 50, 54, 52, 52, 52, 58, 56, 60, 58, 60, 60]}
{"id": "61b3afb9261780b6ea9a", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20071002.0055.LDC2009T13", "relation": "per:title", "token": ["How", "creator", "Fuller", "is", "going", "to", "keep", "things", "interesting", "as", "Ned", "revives/kills", "dead", "people", "each", "week", "and", "continues", "to", "be", "unable", "to", "touch", "Chuck", "will", "be", "one", "of", "the", "TV", "season", "'s", "true", "wonders", "."], "subj_start": 2, "subj_end": 2, "obj_start": 1, "obj_end": 1, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "TITLE", "stanford_pos": ["WRB", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "SET", "SET", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [5, 3, 5, 5, 0, 7, 5, 9, 7, 12, 12, 5, 14, 12, 16, 12, 12, 27, 21, 21, 18, 23, 21, 23, 27, 27, 12, 34, 31, 31, 34, 31, 34, 27, 5], "stanford_deprel": ["advmod", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "ROOT", "mark", "xcomp", "nsubj", "xcomp", "mark", "nsubj", "advcl", "amod", "dobj", "det", "nmod:tmod", "cc", "csubj", "mark", "cop", "xcomp", "mark", "xcomp", "dobj", "aux", "cop", "conj", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod:poss", "case", "amod", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [12, 3, 7, 7, 7, 7, 0, 7, 7, 12, 12, 12, 16, 12, 18, 12, 25, 25, 25, 25, 25, 25, 7, 25, 28, 7, 33, 29, 33, 33, 28, 33, 28, 28, 28]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb91c78c34173", "docid": "bolt-eng-DF-170-181106-8873788", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["far", ",", "three", "sex", "offenders", "-", "George", "Kennedy", ",", "Roy", "Smith", ",", "and", "James", "Easter", "-", "all", "of", "whom", "were", "friends", "of", "Jennifer", "Buchanan", ",", "Nevaeh", "'s", "24-year", "old", "mother", ",", "have", "been", "under", "police", "scrutiny", "and", "jailed", "for", "non-related", "crimes", "while", "the", "investigation", "continues", "more", "than", "a", "week", "after", "5-year", "old", "Nevaeh", "Buchanan", "went", "missing"], "subj_start": 6, "subj_end": 7, "obj_start": 25, "obj_end": 25, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "NNS", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "DT", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG"], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [36, 36, 5, 5, 36, 5, 8, 5, 8, 11, 8, 8, 8, 15, 8, 15, 21, 19, 17, 21, 15, 24, 24, 21, 24, 30, 26, 30, 30, 24, 5, 36, 36, 36, 36, 0, 36, 36, 41, 41, 38, 45, 44, 45, 36, 45, 49, 49, 46, 55, 54, 54, 54, 55, 45, 55], "stanford_deprel": ["advmod", "punct", "nummod", "compound", "nsubj", "punct", "compound", "dep", "punct", "compound", "conj", "punct", "cc", "compound", "conj", "punct", "nsubj", "case", "nmod", "cop", "acl:relcl", "case", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "nmod:poss", "case", "amod", "amod", "appos", "punct", "aux", "cop", "case", "compound", "ROOT", "cc", "conj", "case", "amod", "nmod", "mark", "det", "nsubj", "advcl", "dobj", "case", "det", "nmod", "mark", "amod", "amod", "compound", "nsubj", "advcl", "xcomp"], "ucca_heads": [0, 47, 23, 5, 23, 23, 23, 7, 7, 7, 10, 7, 7, 7, 14, 14, 21, 17, 21, 21, 14, 1, 47, 23, 23, 23, 1, 1, 23, 23, 23, 23, 23, 36, 36, 23, 23, 23, 43, 43, 23, 47, 46, 47, 0, 51, 48, 48, 47, 58, 54, 55, 58, 55, 58, 51]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9953abc16a5", "docid": "APW_ENG_20071205.0615.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Hong", "Kong", "government", "unhappy", "with", "Disneyland", "'", "s", "performance"], "subj_start": 5, "subj_end": 5, "obj_start": 0, "obj_end": 1, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "CITY", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "NN"], "stanford_ner": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [3, 3, 0, 3, 9, 9, 6, 9, 4], "stanford_deprel": ["compound", "compound", "ROOT", "amod", "case", "nmod:poss", "case", "compound", "nmod"], "ucca_heads": [2, 4, 4, 0, 9, 9, 9, 9, 4]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9d8e146364d", "docid": "eng-NG-31-102460-10983846", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Palin", "'s", "two", "months", "in", "the", "national", "media", "spotlight", "raised", "questions", "about", "some", "of", "her", "activities", "as", "governor", "-", "in", "particular", ",", "her", "charging", "the", "state", "$", "17,000", "in", "per", "diem", "payments", "for", "nights", "she", "stayed", "in", "her", "Wasilla", "home", ",", "and", "$", "21,000", "for", "her", "children", "'s", "travel.No", "new", "policies", "have", "been", "set", "for", "those", "practices", ",", "McAllister", "said", "Tuesday", "."], "subj_start": 58, "subj_end": 58, "obj_start": 22, "obj_end": 22, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "POS", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ":", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "$", "CD", "IN", "FW", "FW", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "$", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MONEY", "MONEY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "TIME", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "MONEY", "MONEY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "DATE", "O"], "stanford_head": [4, 1, 4, 10, 9, 9, 9, 9, 4, 60, 10, 13, 11, 16, 16, 13, 18, 10, 18, 21, 18, 10, 24, 10, 26, 24, 28, 24, 32, 32, 30, 28, 34, 32, 36, 34, 40, 40, 40, 36, 24, 24, 44, 54, 51, 47, 51, 47, 51, 51, 44, 54, 54, 24, 57, 57, 54, 60, 60, 0, 60, 60], "stanford_deprel": ["nmod:poss", "case", "nummod", "nsubj", "case", "det", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "ccomp", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct", "case", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "ccomp", "det", "iobj", "dep", "dobj", "case", "amod", "dep", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "case", "nmod:poss", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "cc", "dep", "nsubjpass", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod:poss", "case", "compound", "amod", "nmod", "aux", "auxpass", "conj", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "nmod:tmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [4, 1, 4, 10, 9, 9, 9, 9, 4, 0, 10, 16, 16, 13, 16, 10, 18, 16, 10, 24, 20, 10, 24, 10, 26, 24, 24, 27, 32, 32, 32, 27, 34, 32, 36, 34, 40, 40, 40, 36, 10, 43, 10, 43, 49, 49, 49, 47, 56, 53, 56, 56, 56, 10, 59, 59, 56, 10, 62, 10, 62, 62]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9d3a80182be", "docid": "APW_ENG_20100824.0028", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Adding", "Dow", "and", "P&G", "gives", "the", "2012", "London", "Olympics", "11", "top-tier", "sponsors", "including", "Acer", ",", "Atos", "Origin", ",", "Coca-Cola", ",", "GE", ",", "McDonald", "'s", ",", "Omega", ",", "Panasonic", ",", "Samsung", "and", "Visa", "."], "subj_start": 29, "subj_end": 29, "obj_start": 18, "obj_end": 18, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["VBG", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNPS", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "DATE", "LOCATION", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [5, 1, 2, 2, 0, 12, 12, 12, 12, 12, 12, 5, 14, 12, 14, 17, 14, 14, 14, 14, 14, 14, 14, 23, 14, 14, 14, 14, 14, 14, 14, 14, 5], "stanford_deprel": ["csubj", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "ROOT", "det", "nummod", "compound", "compound", "nummod", "amod", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "conj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "conj", "case", "punct", "conj", "punct", "conj", "punct", "conj", "cc", "conj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [0, 1, 2, 2, 1, 9, 9, 9, 5, 14, 14, 5, 16, 14, 16, 16, 18, 16, 21, 16, 16, 16, 16, 27, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9acd07e3698", "docid": "LTW_ENG_20081218.0064.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Malia", "Obama", ",", "10", ",", "once", "told", "``", "Access", "Hollywood", "''", "that", "she", "was", "looking", "forward", "to", "decorating", "her", "room", "at", "the", "White", "House", "."], "subj_start": 12, "subj_end": 12, "obj_start": 9, "obj_end": 9, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "CITY", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "RB", "VBD", "``", "NN", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 7, 2, 2, 2, 7, 0, 7, 10, 7, 7, 15, 15, 15, 7, 15, 18, 15, 20, 18, 24, 24, 24, 20, 7], "stanford_deprel": ["compound", "nsubj", "punct", "amod", "punct", "advmod", "ROOT", "punct", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "mark", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "advmod", "mark", "xcomp", "nmod:poss", "dobj", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [7, 1, 1, 1, 7, 7, 0, 7, 7, 9, 7, 15, 15, 15, 7, 15, 18, 15, 20, 18, 23, 23, 20, 23, 23]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb90a9181c383", "docid": "APW_ENG_20071128.1001.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Hubbard", "was", "a", "low-profile", "economic", "adviser", "to", "the", "president", "whose", "strength", "came", "from", "his", "closeness", "to", "Bush", "."], "subj_start": 13, "subj_end": 13, "obj_start": 16, "obj_end": 16, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O"], "stanford_head": [6, 6, 6, 6, 6, 0, 9, 9, 6, 11, 12, 9, 15, 15, 12, 17, 15, 6], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubj", "cop", "det", "amod", "amod", "ROOT", "case", "det", "nmod", "nmod:poss", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 0, 8, 8, 8, 2, 11, 11, 8, 14, 14, 8, 17, 17, 14, 19, 17, 19]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb98637719ca1", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20080518.0368.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "country", "has", "been", "under", "emergency", "rule", "since", "January", "11", "last", "year", ",", "when", "polls", "were", "cancelled", "after", "months", "of", "violence", "over", "vote-rigging", "allegations", "made", "by", "the", "Awami", "League", "against", "Zia", "'s", "Bangladesh", "Nationalist", "Party", "-LRB-", "BNP", "-RRB-", "."], "subj_start": 27, "subj_end": 28, "obj_start": 32, "obj_end": 34, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "JJ", "NNP", "-LRB-", "NNP", "-RRB-", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "PERSON", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 7, 7, 7, 7, 7, 0, 9, 7, 9, 12, 9, 9, 17, 17, 17, 9, 19, 17, 21, 19, 24, 24, 21, 24, 29, 29, 29, 25, 35, 35, 31, 35, 35, 25, 37, 35, 37, 7], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "nsubj", "aux", "cop", "case", "compound", "ROOT", "case", "nmod", "nummod", "amod", "dep", "punct", "advmod", "nsubjpass", "auxpass", "acl:relcl", "case", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "case", "compound", "nmod", "acl", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "case", "nmod:poss", "case", "compound", "amod", "nmod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [0, 1, 7, 7, 7, 7, 17, 9, 7, 9, 9, 9, 17, 21, 17, 17, 0, 21, 21, 19, 17, 26, 26, 21, 26, 30, 30, 27, 30, 35, 35, 33, 27, 35, 35, 35, 35, 35, 35]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9112a6a5bfc", "docid": "APW_ENG_20070101.0616.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Kevin", "Doyle", "scored", "twice", "to", "lead", "Reading", "to", "a", "6-0", "mauling", "of", "struggling", "West", "Ham", ";", "Tottenham", "drew", "1-1", "at", "Portsmouth", ";", "and", "Blackburn", "won", "3-0", "at", "Wigan", "."], "subj_start": 23, "subj_end": 23, "obj_start": 13, "obj_end": 14, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "LOCATION", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "NNP", ":", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 3, 0, 3, 6, 3, 6, 11, 11, 11, 7, 13, 11, 15, 13, 3, 18, 3, 18, 21, 18, 3, 3, 25, 3, 25, 28, 25, 3], "stanford_deprel": ["compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "advmod", "mark", "xcomp", "xcomp", "case", "det", "amod", "nmod", "mark", "acl", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "nsubj", "conj", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "punct", "cc", "nsubj", "conj", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [3, 1, 0, 3, 6, 3, 6, 13, 13, 10, 6, 16, 16, 13, 16, 3, 20, 3, 21, 25, 20, 3, 29, 29, 3, 30, 34, 29, 34]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9ec7f2a5771", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20100514.0424", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "New", "South", "Wales", "Waratahs", "booked", "a", "prized", "berth", "in", "the", "Super", "14", "finals", "with", "an", "easy", "32-16", "win", "over", "the", "Wellington", "Hurricanes", "on", "Friday", "in", "Sydney", "."], "subj_start": 1, "subj_end": 4, "obj_start": 26, "obj_end": 26, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "CITY", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "DATE", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [5, 5, 5, 5, 6, 0, 9, 9, 6, 14, 14, 14, 14, 9, 18, 18, 18, 6, 18, 23, 23, 23, 19, 25, 19, 27, 25, 6], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "ROOT", "det", "amod", "dobj", "case", "det", "compound", "nummod", "nmod", "case", "det", "amod", "nmod", "acl", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 0, 2, 2, 2, 0, 9, 9, 6, 14, 14, 14, 12, 6, 6, 17, 6, 18, 17, 24, 24, 21, 24, 27, 6, 29, 27, 29]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9726b8d67d8", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20100516.0467", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["``", "We", "have", "received", "many", "proposals", "and", "we", "are", "considering", "them", ",", "''", "Iran", "'s", "atomic", "chief", ",", "Ali", "Akbar", "Salehi", ",", "was", "quoted", "as", "saying", "on", "Saturday", "in", "local", "media", "."], "subj_start": 18, "subj_end": 20, "obj_start": 27, "obj_end": 27, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "DATE", "stanford_pos": ["``", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "''", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [24, 4, 4, 24, 6, 4, 4, 10, 10, 4, 10, 24, 24, 17, 14, 17, 24, 17, 21, 21, 17, 17, 24, 0, 26, 24, 28, 26, 31, 31, 26, 24], "stanford_deprel": ["punct", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "amod", "dobj", "cc", "nsubj", "aux", "conj", "dobj", "punct", "punct", "nmod:poss", "case", "amod", "nsubjpass", "punct", "compound", "compound", "appos", "punct", "auxpass", "ROOT", "mark", "advcl", "case", "nmod", "case", "amod", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [26, 4, 4, 26, 6, 4, 10, 10, 10, 26, 10, 26, 26, 17, 14, 17, 19, 19, 24, 19, 19, 24, 24, 26, 24, 0, 28, 24, 31, 31, 24, 31]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9cbc6ad6459", "docid": "CNA_ENG_20081230.0008.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "Mainland", "Affairs", "Council", "-LRB-", "MAC", "-RRB-", "announced", "Monday", "that", "the", "government", "will", "cancel", "the", "current", "quota", "of", "500", "per", "month", "for", "applications", "by", "Chinese", "spouses", "for", "Taiwanese", "ID", "cards", "."], "subj_start": 1, "subj_end": 3, "obj_start": 8, "obj_end": 8, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "DATE", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "-LRB-", "NNP", "-RRB-", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [4, 4, 4, 8, 6, 4, 6, 0, 8, 14, 12, 14, 14, 8, 17, 17, 14, 19, 17, 21, 14, 23, 14, 26, 26, 23, 30, 30, 30, 23, 8], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "punct", "appos", "punct", "ROOT", "nmod:tmod", "mark", "det", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "det", "amod", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "case", "amod", "nmod", "case", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [4, 3, 4, 8, 4, 4, 8, 0, 8, 14, 12, 14, 14, 8, 17, 17, 14, 19, 17, 21, 19, 23, 14, 26, 26, 23, 30, 30, 30, 26, 30]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9e8bd73416a", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174572-12947769", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Olivia", "gets", "her", "hair", "cut", "and", "coloured", "at", "the", "award-winning", "Roy", "Teeluck", "Salon", "in", "New", "York", ",", "where", "she", "also", "has", "hair", "extensions", "by", "expert", "Andre", "Davis", "."], "subj_start": 18, "subj_end": 18, "obj_start": 10, "obj_end": 12, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 0, 5, 5, 2, 2, 2, 13, 13, 13, 13, 13, 7, 16, 16, 13, 13, 21, 21, 21, 13, 23, 21, 27, 27, 27, 23, 2], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubj", "ROOT", "nmod:poss", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "conj", "case", "det", "amod", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "case", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "advmod", "nsubj", "advmod", "acl:relcl", "compound", "dobj", "case", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 0, 4, 2, 2, 5, 5, 15, 15, 15, 15, 13, 2, 17, 15, 17, 15, 23, 23, 23, 15, 25, 23, 28, 28, 23, 28, 28]}
{"id": "61b3a783300ccbca1d0c", "docid": "WPB_ENG_20100729.0085", "relation": "per:siblings", "token": ["In", "the", "latest", "Steve", "McPherson", "is", "Gone", "News", ",", "his", "longtime", "entertainment", "attorney", "Tom", "Hoberman", "has", "issued", "a", "deliciously", "vague", "and", "intriguing", "statement", ":"], "subj_start": 3, "subj_end": 4, "obj_start": 13, "obj_end": 14, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [5, 5, 5, 5, 7, 7, 0, 7, 8, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 17, 17, 8, 23, 20, 23, 20, 20, 17, 7], "stanford_deprel": ["case", "det", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "auxpass", "ROOT", "dobj", "punct", "nmod:poss", "amod", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "acl:relcl", "det", "advmod", "amod", "cc", "conj", "dobj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [4, 4, 4, 0, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 13, 13, 13, 14, 4, 14, 17, 4, 23, 20, 23, 13, 23, 17, 23]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9f174a17e62", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20080325.0210.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "victory", "of", "the", "Awami", "National", "Party", ",", "or", "ANP", ",", "was", "welcomed", "by", "Western", "officials", "and", "Pakistanis", "as", "a", "clear", "rejection", "of", "the", "Taliban", "and", "the", "religious", "parties", "that", "backed", "them", "here", "in", "North", "-", "West", "Frontier", "province", "."], "subj_start": 9, "subj_end": 9, "obj_start": 14, "obj_end": 14, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "MISC", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 13, 7, 7, 7, 7, 2, 7, 7, 7, 2, 13, 0, 16, 16, 13, 16, 16, 22, 22, 22, 13, 25, 25, 22, 25, 29, 29, 25, 31, 29, 31, 31, 39, 39, 39, 39, 39, 31, 13], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "nsubjpass", "case", "det", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "cc", "conj", "punct", "auxpass", "ROOT", "case", "amod", "nmod", "cc", "conj", "case", "det", "amod", "nmod", "case", "det", "nmod", "cc", "det", "amod", "conj", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "dobj", "advmod", "case", "compound", "punct", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 22, 5, 5, 2, 5, 5, 5, 10, 5, 22, 13, 22, 16, 16, 13, 16, 16, 22, 21, 22, 0, 25, 25, 21, 25, 29, 29, 25, 31, 29, 31, 31, 39, 38, 35, 35, 39, 31, 39]}
{"id": "61b3af097586be8f7177", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174611-12976276", "relation": "per:religion", "token": ["Devout", "Catholic", "Miss", "Boyle", "has", "been", "at", "the", "centre", "of", "a", "media", "storm", "since", "news", "emerged", "of", "how", "she", "wowed", "Britain", "'s", "Got", "Talent", "judges", "Simon", "Cowell", "and", "Piers", "Morgan", "with", "her", "amazing", "opera", "voice", "."], "subj_start": 3, "subj_end": 3, "obj_start": 1, "obj_end": 1, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "RELIGION", "stanford_pos": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [4, 4, 4, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 0, 13, 13, 13, 9, 16, 16, 9, 20, 20, 20, 16, 27, 21, 27, 27, 27, 27, 20, 27, 30, 27, 35, 35, 35, 35, 20, 9], "stanford_deprel": ["amod", "amod", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "cop", "case", "det", "ROOT", "case", "det", "compound", "nmod", "mark", "nsubj", "advcl", "mark", "advmod", "nsubj", "advcl", "nmod:poss", "case", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "compound", "conj", "case", "nmod:poss", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 4, 4, 6, 6, 0, 13, 9, 13, 9, 13, 13, 6, 16, 16, 6, 20, 20, 20, 16, 25, 21, 25, 20, 26, 20, 26, 26, 26, 29, 35, 35, 35, 35, 20, 35]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb93e2176c834", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20090709.0036", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["``", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "the", "church", "-LRB-", "leaders", "-RRB-", "would", "have", "been", "very", "happy", "about", "it", "-LRB-", "the", "series", "-RRB-", ",", "but", "I", "never", "deal", "with", "those", "people", ",", "''", "he", "said", ",", "though", "he", "has", "met", "the", "California-based", "Miscavige", "a", "few", "times", "."], "subj_start": 35, "subj_end": 35, "obj_start": 40, "obj_end": 40, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["``", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "-LRB-", "NNS", "-RRB-", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "-LRB-", "DT", "NN", "-RRB-", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [33, 5, 5, 5, 33, 7, 15, 9, 7, 9, 15, 15, 15, 15, 5, 17, 15, 20, 20, 5, 20, 5, 5, 26, 26, 5, 29, 29, 26, 33, 33, 33, 0, 33, 38, 38, 38, 33, 41, 41, 38, 44, 44, 38, 33], "stanford_deprel": ["punct", "nsubj", "aux", "neg", "ccomp", "det", "nsubj", "punct", "appos", "punct", "aux", "aux", "cop", "advmod", "ccomp", "case", "nmod", "punct", "det", "dep", "punct", "punct", "cc", "nsubj", "neg", "conj", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "punct", "mark", "nsubj", "aux", "advcl", "det", "amod", "iobj", "det", "amod", "dobj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [5, 5, 5, 5, 33, 7, 15, 7, 7, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 5, 17, 15, 17, 20, 17, 5, 5, 26, 26, 26, 5, 29, 29, 26, 33, 33, 33, 0, 33, 38, 38, 38, 5, 43, 43, 38, 46, 46, 38, 46]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb920767d9d4f", "docid": "LTW_ENG_20080522.0041.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "restaurant", "survey", "company", "Zagat", "has", "even", "teamed", "up", "with", "the", "health", "benefits", "company", "Wellpoint", "Inc.", ",", "parent", "company", "of", "Anthem", "Blue", "Cross", ",", "to", "provide", "Blue", "Cross", "members", "with", "an", "online", "tool", "to", "evaluate", "doctors", "."], "subj_start": 4, "subj_end": 4, "obj_start": 14, "obj_end": 15, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [5, 5, 5, 5, 8, 8, 8, 0, 8, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16, 16, 8, 16, 19, 16, 23, 23, 23, 19, 16, 26, 8, 29, 29, 26, 33, 33, 33, 26, 35, 33, 35, 8], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "aux", "advmod", "ROOT", "compound:prt", "case", "det", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "appos", "case", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "mark", "xcomp", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "case", "det", "amod", "nmod", "mark", "acl", "dobj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [4, 3, 4, 5, 0, 8, 8, 26, 8, 15, 15, 13, 14, 15, 0, 15, 15, 19, 15, 21, 19, 21, 21, 26, 26, 0, 29, 27, 26, 33, 33, 33, 26, 35, 33, 35, 35]}
{"id": "61b3aeb6b09271567c6a", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174592-12943012", "relation": "per:age", "token": ["This", "is", "TELEVISIONISTA", "Read", "more", "about", "AMERICAN", "IDOL", "Kim", ",", "a", "25-year-old", "from", "Saratoga", ",", "Calif", "known", "for", "insisting", "to", "perform", "barefoot", ",", "was", "the", "first", "one", "cut", "on", "Thursday", "after", "failing", "to", "impress", "even", "Paula", "Abdul", "with", "his", "rendition", "of", "``", "Careless", "Whisper", "''", "by", "George", "Michael", "."], "subj_start": 8, "subj_end": 8, "obj_start": 11, "obj_end": 11, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "NUMBER", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "MISC", "PERSON", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORDINAL", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "stanford_head": [4, 4, 4, 0, 4, 9, 9, 9, 5, 9, 12, 9, 14, 12, 14, 14, 16, 19, 17, 21, 19, 21, 14, 28, 28, 28, 28, 4, 30, 28, 32, 28, 34, 32, 37, 37, 34, 40, 40, 34, 44, 44, 44, 40, 44, 48, 48, 40, 4], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubj", "aux", "nsubj", "ROOT", "dobj", "case", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "det", "appos", "case", "nmod", "punct", "appos", "acl", "mark", "advcl", "mark", "xcomp", "dobj", "punct", "cop", "det", "amod", "nummod", "dep", "case", "nmod", "mark", "advcl", "mark", "xcomp", "advmod", "compound", "dobj", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "case", "punct", "amod", "nmod", "punct", "case", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [4, 4, 0, 26, 4, 7, 4, 7, 3, 26, 26, 26, 16, 4, 16, 16, 16, 21, 26, 23, 21, 23, 26, 0, 30, 30, 30, 26, 32, 26, 36, 36, 36, 26, 38, 36, 38, 42, 42, 36, 45, 45, 42, 45, 42, 49, 42, 49, 49]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9a1dc0642e9", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20081223.0152.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["In", "contrast", "to", "Bermuda", ",", "where", "Covidien", "has", "just", "five", "employees", ",", "Covidien", "already", "has", "five", "factories", "and", "nearly", "2,000", "employees", "in", "Ireland", "."], "subj_start": 12, "subj_end": 12, "obj_start": 3, "obj_end": 3, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "LOCATION", "stanford_pos": ["IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 15, 4, 2, 4, 8, 8, 4, 10, 11, 8, 15, 15, 15, 0, 17, 15, 17, 20, 21, 17, 23, 21, 15], "stanford_deprel": ["case", "nmod", "case", "nmod", "punct", "advmod", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "advmod", "nummod", "dobj", "punct", "nsubj", "advmod", "ROOT", "nummod", "dobj", "cc", "advmod", "nummod", "conj", "case", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [15, 1, 1, 0, 8, 8, 8, 0, 11, 11, 8, 8, 15, 15, 8, 17, 15, 17, 21, 21, 17, 23, 21, 23]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb92adb5f457c", "docid": "eng-NG-31-142885-10105592", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["The", "truth", "is", "that", "Muslim", "convert", "and", "Democrat", "Andre", "Carson", "was", "elected", "to", "serve", "not", "because", "he", "is", "a", "Muslim", "but", "because", "the", "overwhelmingly", "Christian", "electorate", "in", "Indiana", "believes", "he", "is", "the", "right", "person", "for", "the", "job", "."], "subj_start": 16, "subj_end": 16, "obj_start": 8, "obj_end": 9, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "VBP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 3, 0, 12, 6, 12, 6, 10, 10, 6, 12, 3, 14, 12, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 14, 20, 29, 26, 25, 26, 29, 28, 26, 20, 34, 34, 34, 34, 29, 37, 37, 34, 3], "stanford_deprel": ["det", "nsubj", "ROOT", "mark", "amod", "nsubjpass", "cc", "compound", "compound", "conj", "auxpass", "ccomp", "mark", "xcomp", "dep", "mark", "nsubj", "cop", "det", "advcl", "cc", "mark", "det", "advmod", "amod", "nsubj", "case", "nmod", "conj", "nsubj", "cop", "det", "amod", "ccomp", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [0, 0, 1, 12, 6, 12, 6, 9, 6, 9, 12, 2, 12, 12, 16, 14, 18, 2, 20, 18, 29, 21, 26, 26, 26, 29, 28, 26, 2, 31, 29, 34, 34, 31, 37, 37, 34, 37]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb966e0fc0c7c", "docid": "APW_ENG_20070427.0053.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["``", "I", "felt", "that", "it", "was", "a", "good", "collaboration", ",", "''", "said", "William", "Anderson", ",", "author", "of", "several", "Wilder", "biographies", "and", "related", "histories", "and", "a", "board", "member", "of", "the", "Wilder", "Home", "Association", "that", "operates", "the", "Mansfield", "site", "."], "subj_start": 12, "subj_end": 13, "obj_start": 18, "obj_end": 18, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["``", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "''", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [12, 3, 12, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 3, 12, 12, 0, 14, 12, 14, 14, 20, 20, 20, 16, 20, 23, 20, 16, 27, 27, 16, 32, 32, 32, 32, 27, 34, 27, 37, 37, 34, 12], "stanford_deprel": ["punct", "nsubj", "ccomp", "mark", "nsubj", "cop", "det", "amod", "ccomp", "punct", "punct", "ROOT", "compound", "nsubj", "punct", "appos", "case", "amod", "compound", "nmod", "cc", "amod", "conj", "cc", "det", "compound", "conj", "case", "det", "compound", "compound", "nmod", "nsubj", "acl:relcl", "det", "compound", "dobj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [12, 12, 0, 3, 3, 23, 9, 9, 23, 12, 12, 0, 12, 13, 13, 13, 20, 20, 20, 16, 20, 23, 12, 23, 27, 27, 23, 32, 32, 32, 32, 27, 34, 32, 37, 37, 34, 37]}
{"id": "61b3a9d0d1685fa9a115", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20071124.0016.LDC2009T13", "relation": "per:children", "token": ["He", "is", "survived", "by", "his", "wife", "of", "63", "years", ",", "Josephine", "Robinson", "McNair", ",", "of", "Columbia", ";", "a", "son", ",", "Robert", "E.", "Jr.", ",", "of", "Columbia", ";", "three", "daughters", ",", "Robin", "Lee", "Howell", "and", "Corinne", "Godshall", ",", "of", "Myrtle", "Beach", ",", "S.C.", ",", "and", "Claudia", "Crawford", "McNair", ",", "of", "Jamestown", ",", "S.C.", ";", "six", "grandchildren", ";", "and", "one", "great-grandchild", "."], "subj_start": 10, "subj_end": 12, "obj_start": 30, "obj_end": 32, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ":", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "CD", "NNS", ":", "CC", "CD", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [3, 3, 0, 6, 6, 3, 9, 9, 6, 6, 13, 13, 6, 6, 16, 6, 6, 19, 6, 19, 23, 23, 19, 19, 26, 19, 19, 29, 19, 29, 33, 33, 29, 33, 36, 33, 29, 40, 40, 29, 40, 40, 40, 40, 47, 47, 40, 47, 50, 47, 50, 50, 19, 55, 19, 19, 19, 59, 19, 3], "stanford_deprel": ["nsubjpass", "auxpass", "ROOT", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "case", "nummod", "nmod", "punct", "compound", "compound", "appos", "punct", "case", "nmod", "punct", "det", "dep", "punct", "compound", "compound", "appos", "punct", "case", "nmod", "punct", "nummod", "conj", "punct", "compound", "compound", "appos", "cc", "compound", "conj", "punct", "case", "compound", "nmod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "cc", "compound", "compound", "conj", "punct", "case", "nmod", "punct", "appos", "punct", "nummod", "conj", "punct", "cc", "nummod", "conj", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [3, 3, 11, 11, 6, 11, 9, 9, 6, 11, 0, 11, 11, 11, 16, 11, 11, 19, 21, 21, 11, 21, 21, 21, 26, 21, 11, 11, 11, 11, 11, 31, 31, 31, 31, 35, 11, 0, 11, 39, 11, 11, 11, 31, 11, 38, 38, 11, 50, 31, 50, 50, 11, 55, 61, 61, 61, 61, 11, 61]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9506e6d82c8", "docid": "eng-WL-11-174611-12970821", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["Though", "there", "had", "been", "speculation", "about", "Mr.", "Cowell", "'s", "status", "with", "the", "show", "for", "several", "weeks", ",", "he", "said", "that", "he", "had", "only", "formally", "reached", "an", "agreement", "with", "Fox", "``", "at", "half-past-10", "", "this", "morning", "to", "bring", "another", "reality", "series", ",", "``", "The", "X", "Factor", ",", "''", "to", "the", "network", "next", "year", "."], "subj_start": 7, "subj_end": 7, "obj_start": 14, "obj_end": 15, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "DURATION", "stanford_pos": ["IN", "EX", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "``", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "``", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "''", "TO", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O"], "stanford_head": [5, 5, 5, 5, 19, 10, 8, 10, 8, 5, 13, 13, 10, 16, 16, 10, 19, 19, 0, 25, 25, 25, 24, 25, 19, 27, 25, 29, 27, 27, 33, 33, 30, 35, 33, 37, 33, 40, 40, 37, 33, 41, 45, 45, 42, 45, 46, 50, 50, 47, 52, 50, 50], "stanford_deprel": ["mark", "expl", "aux", "cop", "advcl", "case", "compound", "nmod:poss", "case", "nmod", "case", "det", "nmod", "case", "amod", "nmod", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "mark", "nsubj", "aux", "advmod", "advmod", "ccomp", "det", "dobj", "case", "nmod", "punct", "case", "amod", "root", "det", "nmod:tmod", "mark", "acl", "det", "compound", "dobj", "punct", "root", "det", "compound", "root", "punct", "root", "case", "det", "root", "amod", "nmod:tmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [10, 5, 5, 5, 0, 5, 0, 7, 7, 5, 13, 13, 10, 16, 16, 10, 5, 19, 5, 25, 25, 25, 25, 25, 19, 27, 25, 29, 25, 25, 34, 25, 25, 37, 25, 25, 54, 42, 42, 45, 45, 45, 5, 45, 45, 45, 45, 52, 52, 45, 7, 5, 54]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9277d8a684e", "docid": "NYT_ENG_20071109.0135.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["--", "Guest", "high-profile", "Professional", "Rodeo", "Cowboys", "Association", "athletes", ",", "including", "defending", "world", "all-around", "champion", "Trevor", "Brazile", "and", "seven-time", "team", "roping", "world", "champion", "Clay", "O'Brien", "Cooper"], "subj_start": 3, "subj_end": 6, "obj_start": 22, "obj_end": 24, "subj_type": "ORGANIZATION", "obj_type": "PERSON", "stanford_pos": [":", "NN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "VBG", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "stanford_head": [0, 8, 8, 8, 8, 8, 8, 1, 8, 8, 10, 16, 16, 16, 16, 11, 16, 25, 25, 25, 25, 25, 25, 25, 16], "stanford_deprel": ["ROOT", "compound", "amod", "amod", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nsubj", "punct", "acl", "xcomp", "compound", "amod", "compound", "compound", "dobj", "cc", "amod", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "compound", "conj"], "ucca_heads": [10, 10, 10, 10, 6, 6, 6, 0, 10, 19, 17, 17, 19, 19, 10, 19, 17, 28, 26, 28, 28, 29, 17, 29, 29]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb958001b53b3", "docid": "AFP_ENG_20081121.0439.LDC2009T13", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["``", "The", "`", "flash", "'", "November", "eurozone", "service", "sector", "and", "manufacturing", "purchasing", "managers", "'", "surveys", "-LRB-", "heightens", "-RRB-", "concern", "that", "the", "eurozone", "'s", "recession", "is", "deepening", ",", "''", "he", "added", "."], "subj_start": 28, "subj_end": 28, "obj_start": 5, "obj_end": 5, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "DATE", "stanford_pos": ["``", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "-LRB-", "NNS", "-RRB-", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [30, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 19, 9, 13, 13, 9, 13, 19, 17, 15, 17, 30, 26, 22, 24, 22, 26, 26, 19, 30, 30, 30, 0, 30], "stanford_deprel": ["punct", "det", "punct", "compound", "punct", "compound", "compound", "compound", "nmod:poss", "cc", "compound", "compound", "conj", "case", "compound", "punct", "appos", "punct", "nsubj", "mark", "det", "nmod:poss", "case", "nsubj", "aux", "ccomp", "punct", "punct", "nsubj", "ROOT", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [15, 15, 15, 2, 2, 9, 9, 9, 2, 2, 12, 13, 15, 15, 0, 15, 15, 15, 15, 26, 22, 24, 22, 26, 26, 19, 15, 15, 30, 15, 30]}
{"id": "61b3a65fb9bb1419f614", "docid": "eng-WL-111-174637-12996181", "relation": "no_relation", "token": ["More", "news", "now", "John", ",", "and", "now", "I", "am", "shocked", ".", "Forest", "wanting", "loan", "deals", ",", "heard", "that", "on", "east", "midlands", "today", "last", "night", ",", "but", "brining", "in", "George", "Boyd", "is", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "shock", ".", "Why", "have", "you", "let", "him", "go", ",", "in", "my", "view", "he", "is", "one", "of", "your", "prize", "assets", "."], "subj_start": 41, "subj_end": 41, "obj_start": 2, "obj_end": 2, "subj_type": "PERSON", "obj_type": "DATE", "stanford_pos": ["RBR", "NN", "RB", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ".", "NNP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ".", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "stanford_ner": ["O", "O", "DATE", "PERSON", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "TIME", "TIME", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "stanford_head": [2, 41, 4, 17, 4, 4, 10, 10, 10, 4, 4, 15, 15, 15, 4, 4, 2, 31, 21, 21, 31, 21, 24, 22, 21, 21, 21, 30, 30, 27, 17, 33, 31, 36, 36, 33, 2, 41, 41, 41, 0, 43, 41, 43, 47, 47, 43, 50, 50, 47, 54, 54, 54, 50, 41], "stanford_deprel": ["amod", "nsubj", "advmod", "nsubj", "punct", "cc", "advmod", "nsubjpass", "auxpass", "conj", "punct", "compound", "amod", "compound", "conj", "punct", "acl:relcl", "mark", "case", "amod", "nmod", "nmod:tmod", "amod", "dep", "punct", "cc", "conj", "case", "compound", "nmod", "ccomp", "det", "nsubj", "case", "det", "nmod", "punct", "advmod", "aux", "nsubj", "ROOT", "nsubj", "ccomp", "punct", "case", "nmod:poss", "nmod", "nsubj", "cop", "acl:relcl", "case", "nmod:poss", "compound", "nmod", "punct"], "ucca_heads": [2, 0, 2, 2, 2, 10, 10, 10, 10, 2, 2, 13, 2, 15, 13, 2, 2, 17, 21, 21, 17, 17, 24, 17, 2, 27, 2, 29, 27, 29, 2, 33, 36, 33, 36, 31, 2, 41, 41, 41, 2, 41, 41, 43, 47, 47, 49, 49, 43, 49, 50, 50, 50, 0, 2]}
